Hello brothers, I am your brother Gaurav and I
welcome you to our new video. I
hope you will find this video very
good and brother, this video is going to be very
useful for you. So,
if you too, like me, are worried
about the build quality of this car, the way
it is, and look at its
condition, brother, it is okay, it broke from here, it
broke from here, and its guard, yes,
its belt guard, that too, brother, is
broken, so the condition of the belt has also
deteriorated a lot, so brother,
when there is so much problem in our mind, only one
thing comes to mind, the first thing that you will do is,
brother, you will go to the showroom and
try to get it repaired, instead of making an
insurance claim, what will you have to do in that,
you will meet the technician, he will
tell you its cost, so brother, something
around, if I talk about it, like I
also did this, I also went to the insurance, that is, Ola
showroom, I
talked to the technician there, after talking to him,
I came to know that brother, this is
our guard of Ola, the cost of it will be for
you.  It will cost at least ₹1000000,
this is also its cost and brother, the
same is the case with the guard, okay, so brother, this is such a huge
expense, that is, if you see, it will
cost roughly 5,55,600, so brother,
without creating so much fuss, what have we done normally,
brother, today we have made an insurance
claim for the Ola, so brother, I was
watching videos related to Ola,
and brother, I will also give this Ola to you
because I have already
submitted its insurance for claim yesterday, so
I have also received a call from there
that you should go to the nearest Ola showroom and park it
there,
after that a team will come for inspection, I do
n't know how many people are there in the team, brother, I
think there will be only one person who
will inspect it, and
after that its cost will be determined, according to that cost,
whatever material is there in it will be required, so
brother, now I would like to tell you one small thing, what needs to be done,
okay, so
Brother, the first thing you have to do is you have to find out whether your
Ola is insured with the company
because brother, now
its insurance is online, it is digital
insurance, so not everyone knows that, the
company will give you the RC and will
provide it, but you may not
know which company the insurance is with,
like I had this problem, I hope it
may not be with you, but I had
this problem that
I did not know which company my Ola was insured with, so
I will tell you what I did right now by
going to the mobile screen, brothers, although it is
quite easy to get Ola insurance done, but some of
my brothers face a lot of problems in this,
their solution is going to be told in this video,
so brother, see this is the screen of some of our
mobiles, now what you have to do is that
some of my brothers are such that they do not
know which
company their Ola insurance is with because I also do not know
brother, there will be some like me too, what do they have to do
brother, you do not have to do anything normally,
after the electric power goes off, something like this will appear in
front of you, so brother, one
thing has to be kept in mind in this, how did this kind of
thing come because brother  This is the mobile number with
which I had
registered it while taking my account in the company. So whenever
I use the app for my work, simply to
unlock it
or to see something,
this mobile number of mine is registered in it. So this
app knows my total
information, so it directly
opened it and gave me all my documents. It gave it to
me after loading. Now,
we simply don't have to do anything, go to the 's1 pra jatu' where it is
written.
Now it will take a little
time to load, but it will load.
After that, you have to scroll
down and brother, it is written here,
View Insurance Policy, you have to
click on it. So brother, see, this is your
insurance. Brother, I made a small mistake,
which I realized while making the
video. That mistake was that
brother, what I was calling insurance is
digital insurance, not digital insurance. The
information was wrong, so I
would like to say sorry for that, but brother,
you will see
this in all the videos that you have seen in the future.  It is okay to count only the digit insurance,
brother, these things have been
finalized here, now we have come to know about our digit insurance,
after that what do we have to do,
after that we have to come to brother, here
you have to type your digit insurance, like my
digit is yours, if it is any other, then you simply have to
type it there, here digit
j is my digit, Digit Insurance customer
care, I did it here, so brother, here you have
its number, from here you have to
copy it and you have to call them,
after the call I have told you the information,
what all will they ask you in the video,
but brother, what will happen after that, that is all I
talked about, I have
included their photo in it also, so brother,
you will get some such link in which the
company people will tell you that your
damaged part has come here, so
I have to click on this link, then it will
ask you for your photo here, it will ask for your RC,
your driving license, your PAN
card, all these documents of yours will be required here,
but brother, I am telling you one thing in the video,
this is our  Its VRO has also been done, the
repair order of your
vehicle has been passed,
I have submitted it to my Ola,
but there was a small fault in it,
brother, the technician there
told me that look sir, you should
not leave your Ola here, what happens is that when
you make an Ola claim, then your Digit
Insurance people will say that
one of our people will come there and will
check it thoroughly whether any problem part is damaged inside your Ola or any of
your scooter, then an
estimate will be made for you, that estimate will be passed, so
brother, see, our estimate has been passed, the
vehicle repair order,
it comes in your
final list that
what all things are faulty in your Ola or any of your things, so
brother, I would like to add a small point in this,
I got this VRO checked, so in
my video you must have seen
that three things of mine, but what did they do
here  That here we have done only two
things,
I will also tell you about how I got these done for three,
that too will become three,
you can see in your video, here
we have only one plastic metal set
trim and LH brake lever head, our count is
not there in this, so there is no problem in that
brother, we will get that done, but brother, what happened in this,
now when I came to know about this, I told the person who had
called me last time
that brother, this is yours and you
send us the documents, a personal call will come in
which you will have to send the photo of the damaged part,
so I called him again
and brother, I told him that sir, there is a
problem by doing this and that, you did not do the main thing,
I
shot a video and uploaded it to them, brother, he
finalized that thing also for us,
stay tuned to the video, I am going to give some more information further
that when you are getting an Ola insurance
claim done, what things you have to take
care of, which you will talk about there on the call
and there are other things too brothers,
after this procedure your work will be done,
but in this you will have to take care of two things  You will have to be very
careful about this. What should I say, I will tell you a few
things, after that you should see that
whenever you complete all these procedures for insurance,
after that you will get
a call from the insurance company from which you got the insurance, in that
you will have to tell everything like
when did your accident happen, where did it happen, how did it happen,
is there any FIR, how much, which side is
damaged, how is it, how is it, so in that brother
you will have to use a little bit of your brain, brother you will have to
lie a little, that's all, look
my brother, you think that brother, just tell that it happened
yesterday, brother, make an insurance claim today,
no, no, it will not work like this brother,
you can make an insurance claim after about 48 hours, that
means
if I am making an insurance claim today, then
if I tell them to the company people
that brother, brother, I had a
small accident like this, then I will give that two days
old and you have to keep one thing in mind,
write it down on pen and paper,
when you get a call, do not go back and forth,
your insurance claim will not be processed if
in the eyes of the company you yourself do
not trust your words, it will not be processed at all
if  You know that brother, as I
told you that you have to tell something that is two days old,
like if I am making an insurance claim today, then
you have to tell that I had an
accident two days ago, you must keep this thing in mind,
you have to pay a lot of attention to the timing in it,
you also have to
tell that brother, brother, brother, did you get injured, did you file an
FIR, then you simply have to say
that brother, sir, it was not such a long story,
a car was coming from the front, whatever it is, you can
tell it in whatever way you want and you do
n't have to tell about any FIR, they ask you for the FIR there,
but even if you don't file the FIR, there is no
problem in it, it will
work, brothers, if you take care of these things
properly, then you will
not have any problem in it, your insurance
claim will be done, so much brother, right now I do
n't know when the insurance claim has been done,
when will the material come, when will it be, I am a
little confused about when it will be done, whatever it will be, if it happens then
I will tell you
whatever it is in our hands and brother, in a video,
you can see its condition properly, right now
this  In what condition is it, you will find it broken,
ours is also broken, it is
making a lot of noise, I will also play a video clip of
how its head is making noise, it is
making a very bad noise,
okay and our belt guard is also
broken, which is the belt guard, now when
it comes after claim, all the work that needs to be done on it will be done,
after that I will
make a video once again for you that brother, the
work done by the LA people in our company,
how have they used the materials, are they good
or bad, if you have any problem, you can
ask anything, you can do it in the comments,
brother, whatever comments my
brothers have, if there is any question,
brother, I will clear it, brother, now
if you liked this video, then
like this video, subscribe to our channel
and see you brother, today it was
given, I will put a video of that too,
brother, we have parked our Ola in the showroom,
after that we will talk, when it
comes, till then we will meet
in some next video and till then goodbye, see
you Tata